survivingateacherssalary.com 2017-11-28

# Disclosure & Privacy Policy for Surviving a Teacher's Salary - Surviving A Teacher's Salary

## Disclosure Policy

_This disclosure policy is valid from 20 August 2010, updated 1/1/2016._

_This blog is a personal blog written and edited by me, Crystal Rapinchuk. This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship,  or other forms of compensation. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics, or posts made in this blog but not the opinions stated or quality. This blog may participate in sponsored posts. That content, advertising space or ambassadorship will always be identified as paid or sponsored content._

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity.

_This blog does contain affiliate links in posts from time to time. This is not to be construed as an endorsement of the company or product, but is merely a way to compensate the blogger for the time taken to scout the deal for the reader. These are not  advertorial posts, they are informational posts pointing to a specific deal or sale._

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

The owner of this website is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner of this website receives compensation for some of my posts or advertisements, she always give her honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this website are purely the her own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

I am a participant in the Amazon Service LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to [www.amazon.com](http://www.amazon.com/) from [www.survivingateacherssalary.com](http://www.survivingateacherssalary.com/). I am also a participate with various ad companies including but not limited to Google Adsense and AdThrive. (see below)

## Privacy Policy 

At [www.survivingateacherssalary.com](http://www.survivingateacherssalary.com/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  We do not share personal information with third parties nor do we store any information about your visit to this blog other than to analyze and optimize your content and reading experience through the use of cookies. You can turn off the use of cookies at anytime by changing your specific browser settings. We are not responsible for republished content from this blog on other blogs or websites without our permission. This privacy policy is subject to change without notice and was last updated on 1/1/2016. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [www.survivingateacherssalary.com](http://www.survivingateacherssalary.com/).  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to [www.survivingateacherssalary.com](http://www.survivingateacherssalary.com/) and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Amazon Service LLC Associates Program  
**I am a participant in the Amazon Service LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to [www.amazon.com](http://www.amazon.com/) from [www.survivingateacherssalary.com](http://www.survivingateacherssalary.com/).

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include but are not limited to ….  
Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Share a Sale  
Linkshare  
Amazon  
AdThrive

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [www.survivingateacherssalary.com](http://www.survivingateacherssalary.com/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, [www.survivingateacherssalary.com](http://www.survivingateacherssalary.com/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
[www.survivingateacherssalary.com](http://www.survivingateacherssalary.com/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

_[www.survivingateacherssalary.com](http://www.survivingateacherssalary.com/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers._

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [www.survivingateacherssalary.com](http://www.survivingateacherssalary.com/)’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
